<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelog xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    tools:ignore="MissingDefaultResource">
    <release version="Beta">
        <change>&lt;b&gt;Breaking Change:&lt;/b&gt; Local Push notifications directly from your Home Assistant instance. The app will need to maintain a consistent websockets connection by using a persistent notification. From the notification you will be able to access websockets settings to adjust the behavior of the connection as well as the notification channel. You are free to minimize the notification channel to hide the icon. If you are on the minimal build you will need to have Home Assistant Core on 2022.2 in order for the notify service call to be created.</change>
        <change>&lt;b&gt;Breaking Change:&lt;/b&gt; The Do Not Disturb sensor is now only available on devices running Android 6 or higher. The sensor was updated to use a documented API rather than the undocumented method used.</change>
        <change>&lt;b&gt;Breaking Change:&lt;/b&gt; The Last Used App sensor will now report its state as the package name to always be unique</change>
        <change>Downloads are now supported in the Home Assistant Frontend</change>
        <change>WiFi State sensor now has instant updates for those devices that did not have it before</change>
        <change>Notification commands for command_activity and command_broadcast_intent now support more types of intent extras</change>
        <change>Add change log dialog to show when the app is updated. Can also be accessed in settings.</change>
        <change>Add notification command to update sensors</change>
        <change>Add option to add a new widget and other design changes to Manage Widgets page</change>
        <change>Minor design changes to Manage Shortcuts and Manage Tiles page</change>
        <change>Add notification channel settings so they are easier to find</change>
        <change>Add icons to settings</change>
        <change>Improve reliability of opening entity information from device controls</change>
        <change>Editing Wear OS Template Tile from phone settings</change>
        <change>Add support for button and input_button domains, tweak climate domain in device controls</change>
        <change>Add support for button and input_button domains in quick settings tiles</change>
        <change>Add In Use sensor for Quest devices</change>
        <change>Minimal version fixes to remove Google dependencies</change>
        <change>Lots of miscellaneous bug fixes</change>
        <change>Dependency updates</change>
    </release>
</changelog>